I'm coming back to the story and why
Scott is that there was an explorer
and he was inspired by the film Scott
of the Antarctic with John Mills
in it
and so he became an explorer and there
aren't that many records left for
polar exploration so he did one of
them which involved I think walking
to one of the poles unaided
and when he came back he was bankrupt
and so because he was obviously a
slightly crazy person he wrote to
John Mills and he said it's your fault
that I'm bankrupt and I'm in a
terrible state and it's your fault and
John Mills said oh come around for
tea which isn't a good thing to do I
don't think to the kind of people
who write to you and say it's your
fault that I've done something and
when it is not your fault but anyway
so this chap went around to have tea
with John Mills and he said I'm in
this total state there's nothing
I can do you know I'm completely
bankrupt
and John Mills said well you're going
to have to talk your way out of it
and he said what do you mean talk
your way out of it. I can't talk my
way out of it.
There's,
you know, the banks are going to
foreclose or whatever the word is on my
mortgage, you know, I'm in a terrible
situation. And John Mills said,
no, come in the bathroom. And so
for the next two, three hours, what
they did was they put together a
speech that this guy could use and he
could go and give us an inspirational
talk and he could use us an
after-dinner speech, etc.
So kind of like John Mills was firmly
of the view that you can talk your
way out of something. Thank you.